時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
향례 지팡구 무예 대회에 출전한 무사시는 이전 대회와는 돌변해서 쾌조의 연승을 한다.
Joining the annual Jipangu Maritial Arts Competition, Musashi keeps winning, changed completely from the previous one.
그러나 그 쯤, 지팡 지배를 꾸미는 육도마왕은 국왕에게서 삼종의 신기를 노려 방패와 곡옥을 빼앗았다.
But meanwhile, Rikudomaoh, who's looking to take the Three Sacred Treasures from the king,
already got the shield and the round jewel.
괴물!
메가톤성이오
A Monster!
Megaton Castle
무사시 씨? 오츠루? 조금 도와줘.
Mr. Musashi and Otsuru, can you help me?
여보. 그런 곳에서 뭐 해?
Dear. What are you doing there?
쉿!
Shh!
내일은 드디어 준결승이구나.
Finally, you have semi-finals tomorrow!
그렇소. 드디어 그 코지로하고 싸울 때가 왔소!
Right-dasu. It's finally time to fight that Kojirō-dasu!
힘내, 무사시 씨. 난 가게 일이 있으니까 응원하러는 못 가지만 마음속으로는 계속 빌고 있어.
Go for it, Mr. Musashi! I have to work in the store and I can't go cheer for you, but I'm still wishing for your victory!
맡겨두시오! 꼭 이겨서 지팡구 제일의 카라쿠리 무예가가 되어 보이겠소!
Leave it to me-dasu! I'll win and become the number one Karakuri martial artist of Jipangu!
그러면...
And then...
그러면?
And then?
그러면, 오츠루, 약속대로 나도... 그거...
And then, Otsuru, as promised, I...
뭐? 잘 안 들려, 무사시 씨.
What is it? I can't hear you, Mr. Musashi.
내, 내 부인으로...
I'd like to have you as my wife...
알고 있었소?!
You already knew-dasu?!
별똥별!
A shooting star!
어떻게든 무사시 씨가 내일 경기에서 이길 수 있도록.
Wishing Mr. Musashi to win in tomorrow's match.
오츠루...
Otsuru...
이래선 우리 응원 따위 필요 없겠는걸?
They won't be needing our cheers, after all!
아, 좋겠네.
They're so romantic.
어, 어이, 안 돼, 이런 곳에선! 부끄럽게.
N- no, not at a place like this! It's embarassing!
괜찮잖아? 부부인데.
Isn't it alright? We're married.
아, 그건 그런데...
Well, that's true...
여보?
Dear?
아카네?
Akane?
여보!
Dear!
뭐야?
What is it?
불길하군.
That's ominous.
안 되지. 별 따위나 바라보고 있을 때가 아니지.
No, it's not the time to be watching stars.
좋아, 내일의 결정타 포즈는 이걸로 갈까.
Well. Should this be my finishing pose tomorrow?
아니, 그래도 이것도 멋지고...
Nah, this looks cool, too...
오, 이것도 좋네.
This is good, too!
(지팡구바레: 니혼바레; 쾌청함)
(jipangbare: twist of nihonbare; clear and cloudless sky)
날이 밝으면 지팡구의 하늘에는 구름 한 점 없이 쾌청하다! 드디어 준결승전이 시작된다!
When the sun rises, the sky of Jipangu is clear and the semi-finals finally begins!
전국 일천만 무예 팬 여러분! 오래 기다리셨습니다!
Welcome, 10 million martial art fans! The waiting is soon over!
무대를 빛내는 대회도 드디어 준결승! 오늘은 특별 게스트로 방송석에 센히메 님을 모였습니다.
The competition on that shining stage is already at semi-finals! Today, we have Senhime as a special guest!
어, 본방?!
Is this live?!
센히메입니다! 신랑 모집중입니다! 잘 부탁드립니다!
Senhime here! Now looking for a husband! Please contact me!
저, 센히메 님, 오늘의 경기, 누가 이기리라 생각됩니까.
Er, Senhime, who do you think will win?
그러게... 뭐, 강한 쪽이 이기고 약한 쪽이 지겠지, 분명!
I wonder... I guess the stronger wins and the weaker loses, probably!
무사시 님. 이 주베, 대전하게 되기를 진심을 다해 빌겠습니다.
Mr. Musashi. I am truly looking for a match with you.
그럼 지금부터 준결승전을 시작하겠습니다.
The semi-finals will begin now!
빨강 코너, 98번 이천일류 무사시!
Red corner: #98 Niten'ichiryū Musashi!
하양 코너, 99번 간류 미스터 코지로!
White corner: #99 Ganryu Mister Kojirō!
-코지로 님!
-무사시 씨!
-Mr. Kojirō!
-Mr. Musashi!
내가 이기고 네가 져도, 네가 지고 내가 이겨도 좋은 경기를 하자꾸나, 무사시.
Even if I win and you lose, or you lose and I win, let's have a good match, Musashi.
물론이오.
Of course-dasu.
어? 내가 이기고 네가 져도, 네가 지고 내가 이겨도...
Huh? Even if I win and you lose, or you lose and I win...
뭣이오! 결국 내가 지는 게 아니오!
What was that-dasu?! I lose in both ways-dasu!
칫. 들켰군.
Tch. You found it out.
당연하오!
Of course-dasu!
시작!
Start!
개문! 개문!
Open the door! Open the door!
뭐, 뭣이? 그게 정말이오? 국왕의 증표인 삼종의 신기를 빼았겼다는 것이.
W- what?! Is it true that the certificate of the king, the Three Sacred Treasures have been stolen?
그렇습니다. 어젯밤 궁전에 침입해 와서... 어떻게든 성검은 지켰습니다만.
Right. They came to invade the palace yesterday night. The sacred sword is safe, though.
그걸 노리고 추격자가 뒤따르고 있습니다.
Enemies are in pursuit of us, looking for that.
이에야스. 나도 부탁한다. 악의 손에서 성검을 지키고 빼앗긴 신기를 되찾아 주어라.
Ieyasu. I'll also ask you to protect the sacred sword from the hands of evil, and recover the stolen treasures.
예. 분부대로 하겠습니다. 어서 무예에 뛰어난 자를 모으겠습니다.
Yessir. Just as you instructed. I will gather people fluent in martial arts.
그런가. 역시 국왕은 이에야스에게 도움을 요청했나.
I see. The king did ask for a help to Ieyasu.
어떻게 하시겠습니까, 육도마왕 님. 아무리 제 몸이 강하다고 해도 에도 성은 난공불락의 성.
What will you do, Lord Rikudomaoh. Even if my body became stronger, Edo Castle is impregnable.
흥. 너같은 신참은 우리 군의 참된 무서움을 모른다!
Hmph. A newcomer like you do not know the true fearfulness of our force!
뭐라?!
What?!
그만해라, 한조.
Stop, Hanzō.
지금은 동료끼리 싸우고 있을 때가 아니다.
This is not the time for internal discord.
아, 알겠습니다.
U- understood.
도쿠간류. 상륙 준비를 해라.
Dokuganryu. Prepare for landing.
예!
Yessir!
제기랄. 마왕 놈. 기억해 둬라.
Damn you, you Maoh. You'll regret this.
이건 대단한 상태! 박력 가득한 배틀입니다!
That is awesome! It's a battle full of force!
가라, 무사시! 때려버려! 코지로도 어서!
Go for it, Musashi! Hit him! Kojirō, you too!
똑바로 해!
Do it properly!
잡았다!
Got you!
꽤 하게 되었구나, 무사시. 그러나 과연 내 츠바메가에시를 피할 수 있을까?
You became better, Musashi. But will you manage to evade my Tsubamegaeshi?
그건 내가 할 말이오! 이천일류 섬광권!
That's my line-dasu! Niten'ichiryū: Flash Sword!
중단!
Stop!
누구냐! 경기를 방해하는 게!
Who dares to interrupt our match?!
이에야스 님!
Lord Ieyasu!
할아버지!
Grandpa!
사정으로 무예 대회는 여기까지 한다.
Driven by the stress of circumstnaces, the martial arts competition will end here.
그런! 우리 승부 아직 안 났소!
No way! Our match is not over-dasu!
문답무용이다! 무사시, 코지로, 주베하고 함께 따라와라.
No questions asked! Musashi, Kojirō, follow me with Jūbee.
이에야스 님!
Lord Ieyasu!
감사합니다!
Thank you!
이제 끝났을까, 준결승.
I wonder if the semi-final match is over.
무사시 씨가 이기도록...
Please let Mr. Musashi be the winner.
오츠루!
Otsuru!
무사시 씨! 아직 시합이!
Mr. Musashi! The match shouldn't be already over!
그럴 때가 아니게 되었소.
We can't do that anymore-dasu.
어?
Huh?
그 한조가 이번엔 지팡구국의 보물을 노리고 있소.
That Hanzō is looking to steal the treasures of Jipangu State this time-dasu.
덕분에 나, 오늘밤부터 성에 묵으며 성 경비를 하게 되었소.
Because of that, I have to stay in the castle from this night and do a guard duty-dasu.
그럼 다시 못 만나게 되는 거네.
Then it means that we can't meet again.
오츠루...
Otsuru...
괜찮소! 엎드리면 코 닿을 데의 에도 성이오. 경비 째고 종종 보러 오오!
It'll be alright-dasu! That Edo Castle is within a stone's throw-dasu. I'll skip the guard duty and come see you-dasu!
그렇네. 나도 매일 단고 보내러 갈게.
That's right. I'll go everyday to give you dangos!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
그래! 그럼 바로 오늘 분량 만들어 줄게.
Right! Let me make today's amount right away.
오츠루 정말 상냥하오!
Otsuru is so kind-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
괜찮아? 무사시 씨!
Are you okay, Mr. Musashi?
누구이오! 돌 던진 바보멍청이는!
What ultra fool threw a stone-dasu?!
아니, 센쨩.
It was you, Sen-chan...
누가 바보멍청이야?
Who's an ultra fool?
아니아니아니아니, 그게...
Nonononono... that's...
단고 따위 사고 있을 때가 아니잖아? 한시라도 빨리 성에 돌아가야 하는데!
It's not the time to buy dangos! We have to go back to the castle as soon as possible!
아니오! 나 오츠루한테 잠시 못 만난다고 말하러 왔을 뿐이오!
No-dasu! I'm here just to tell Otsuru that I can't come to meet her for a while-dasu!
무사시 씨, 이 사람은?
Mr. Musashi, who's this?
같이 여행한 센짱이오.
She's Sen-chan whom I traveled with-dasu.
네가 오츠루구나. 무사시한테 들었어.
You must be Otsuru. Musashi told me about you.
같이 여행을?
Traveled with?
그렇구나. 예쁜 분이네.
I see. She's pretty.
아, 아니, 그런 사실을 말하려면 더 큰 목소리로 말해!
N- no, if you're going to say something that's true, then do it loudly!
그래도 성격 나쁘오.
But her personality is bad-dasu.
뭔 개소리야! 다시 한번 말해봐라!
What are you being stupid about?! Say that again!
알겠소! 센짱은 미인이오!
I get it! You're beautiful, Sen-chan!
-그리고?
-미인에 똑바르고 성격 좋고 부자이고-
-And?
-Beautiful, dead straight, has a good personality, rich,
-아직아직! 부족해!
-그래도!
-Not yet! List more!
-But!
어, 오츠루!
Hey, Otsuru!
오츠루! 단고!
Otsuru! Dangos!
몰라!
I don't care!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
대체 어떻게 된 것이오?
What happened-dasu?
저, 저게 뭐야?!
W- what's that?!
에도토피아에 위기가 다가온다! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
A crisis is approaching Edotopia! Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
이에야스 님. 이 자들이 말씀하신 최강의 카라쿠리 무예가입니까.
Mr. Ieyasu. Are they the strongest Karakuri martial artists that you chose?
이 쪽의 떨떠름한 사내는 아무래도 강해 보이지만, 나머지 둘은 아직 아이 아닙니까.
This glum man does look strong, but aren't the other two still children?
실례하는 할배이오! 이래뵈도 우리는 무예 대회의 준결승까지 갔소!
You're one rude old man-dasu! We just went to the semi-finals of the martial arts contest-dasu!
말을 삼가라, 무사시! 국왕 전하의 어전이다!
Shut your mouth, Musashi! We're at the presence of the Highness!
그래도!
But!
이 자들은 한조하고 몇 번이고 훌륭히 상대해 싸워 왔습니다. 안심하십시오.
These people fought against Hanzō and won for numerous times. Rest assured.
아, 그렇습니까. 이에야스 님이 그렇게 말씀하신다면.
Oh, is that so? If you do certify them...
어쨌든, 국왕 전하, 노림받는 성검을 삼가 볼 수 있습니까.
Anyway, your Highness, can we take a look at the targeted sacred sword?
이것이 그것입니다.
This is it.
이 검 외에도 곡옥과 방패가 있어, 그 셋을 가진 자가 이 지팡구국의 국왕이 됩니다.
Other than this sword, there exist the round jewel and the sword.
The one to have all three of them becomes the king of Jipangu State.
영주님! 큰일입니다. 에도토피아 만에 거대한 성같은 것이 나타났습니다!
Lord! We have a problem! Something giant that looks like a castle has appeared at Edotopia Bay!
뭣이?!
What?!
성이 걸어오오!
A castle is walking towards here-dasu!
한조 놈! 말도 안 되는 것을 가지고 나타났구나!
That Hanzō appeared with something so nonsensical!
이에야스 및 국왕에게 알린다. 바로 성검을 넘겨라. 그러지 않으면 이 메가톤성을 에도 성에 부딪힌다!
Informing to Ieyasu and the king. Hand over the sacred sword, or I'll crash this Megaton Castle to Edo Castle!
아니야! 저 목소리는 한조가 아니야!
That's different! That voice is not Hanzō's!
누구이오, 당신은?!
Who are you-dasu?!
나는 이 세상을 지배하려는 육도마왕의 가신, 도쿠간류다!
I am Dokuganryu, a family member of Rikudomaoh looking to rule over the world!
자, 이에야스, 어서 대답해라. 나는 성미가 급하다.
Ieyasu, answer me right now. I am impatient.
네이놈! 다들 뭘 하나! 응전해라! 절대 성검을 넘길 수는 없다!
You bastard! Everyone! Return the fire! We will not hand over the sacred sword!
뭔 괴물이냐.
What kind of monster is that?!
이에야스 님. 이대로는 위험합니다. 어서 피난을!
Lord Ieyasu. It is dangerous here. You have to take shelter!
멍청한 놈! 나라의 주인이 성에서 달아날 수 있을 것 같나!
You fool! Do you think that the ruler of a country can flee from the castle?
이랴, 쏴라, 쏴라, 막 쏴라!
Hey! Fire, fire, and keep firing!
아, 이대로는 찌부러지겠어!
We'll end up becoming crushed at this rate!
이쪽의 성도 움직일 수 있다면 성 대 성으로 좋은 경기가 가능할 텐데.
If our castle can move too, it would be a good battle between two castles.
그거이오, 그거이오! 이야, 당신도 올바른 소리를 하오!
That's it-dasu, that's it-dasu! You can be right sometimes-dasu!
야, 무사시! 국왕 전하께 뭔 짓을!
Hey, Musashi! What are you doing to the Highness?!
있소, 우리에게도 놈들에게 지지 않을 성이!
We have one-dasu! The castle that will stand up to them!
무사시, 메가톤성에 지지 않을 성이 어디 있다는 거냐?
Musashi, what do you mean by the castle that will stand up to Megaton Castle?
저것이오!
That's it-dasu!
오, 합체성이군. 저거라면 돌아다닐 수 있겠어.
Fusion Castle! That does move!
와, 이게 합체성의 조종석이오!
This must be the cockpit of Fusion Castle!
좋소, 출발이오!
Alright! We're moving forward-dasu!
이걸 상대에게 부딪혀서 쓰러트려 주겠소!
We'll crash this to the enemy and knock it over-dasu!
내 높은 코가...
My pointy nose...
뭔 짓이야, 무사시!
What was that for, Musashi?!
저걸 보시오!
Look at that-dasu!
이거!
Damn!
아, 이대로는 못 지나가오. 기껏 좋은 아이디어라 생각했더니...
We can't go through here-dasu. I thought I had a good idea...
포기하지 마라, 무사시! 이 성은 7개로 분리할 수 있어!
Don't give up, Musashi! This castle can divided into seven!
그래도 7개로 나뉘어도 누가 움직이오. 여기엔 3명밖에 없소.
But who'll move those 7 parts-dasu? There are only 3 here-dasu.
평소하고 다르게 현명한 소리를.
That was unusually clever.
우리가 도웁시다!
We'll help!
제니가탄 두목! 지라이얀! 우시와카 씨! 덤으로 벤케이 씨도!
Boss Zenigatan! Jiraiyan! Mr. Ushiwaka! Mr. Benkei in addition!
난 덤이 아니다!
I am not an addition!
같은 무예가로서 저런 악한 잘못된 행위는 용서할 수 없습니다!
As a fellow martial artist, I cannot forgive an evil wrongdoing like that!
나도야! 최근 체질이 바뀌었더니 나쁜 놈들하고 싸울 생각에 근질근질하다!
Me too! I'm really up for a real fight, since I've changed recently!
에도토피아의 평화를 어지럽히는 놈은 이 제니가탄이 가만둘 수는 없다!
Whoever disrupts the peace of Edotopia will not be forgiven by me, Zenigatan!
다들! 좋소! 카라쿠리 무예가의 우정 파워를 보여주겠소!
Everyone! Alright! We'll show the friendship powers of Karakuri martial artists-dasu!
좋소, 다들! 가오!
Alright, everyone! Let's go-dasu!
에도성을 향해 출발!
Set out for Edo castle!
좋다!
Right!
멀리서 봤는데도 큰데, 가까이서 보니 더욱이 크구나!
It was big when it was far away, but it's even bigger when it got closer!
이에야스 님. 어서 국왕 전하를 안전한 곳으로.
Mr. Ieyasu. We have to get the Highness to somewhere safe.
아니, 이 에도 성이 부서지면 더이상 안전한 곳은 없습니다.
No. If this Edo Castle gets destroyed, there is no more safe place.
아, 무사시, 코지로, 어서 와!
Musashi, Kojirō, hurry up and come!
자, 부서지고 싶지 않으면 순순히 성검을 넘겨라!
If you don't want to have your castle destroyed, then hand over the sacred sword!
거절한다! 누가 네놈 따위를 이 나라의 왕으로 인정할 쏘냐!
I refuse! No fool will acknowledge you bastards as the king of this country!
그럼 죽어라. 성검은 다음에 여유롭게 찾아 주겠다.
Then die. We can always find the sacred sword later in peace.
이제 틀렸어!
We're doomed!
기다리시오!
Stop-dasu!
오, 합체성!
That must be Fusion Castle!
무사시!
Musashi!
이제 이걸로 메가톤성 따위 무섭지 않소!
We aren't afraid of Megaton Castle anymore, since we got this-dasu!
멍청한 놈. 그런 쪼까만 걸로 메가톤성을 이길 수 있을 거라 생각하냐!
You fool! Do you really think that you can defeat Megaton Castle with something that small?!
쪼까만지 어떤지는 이걸 보고 말하시오!
You can judge whether it's small after this-dasu!
이, 이건!
T- that's!
흥, 합체성. 머리 좀 썼구나, 무사시.
Hmph. Fusion Castle. You used your brain for once, Musashi.
보았소? 이 지팡구 무예 대회 궁극의 경기장, 합체성이오!
Did you see-dasu? This is Fusion Castle, the ultimate stadium of Jipangu Martial Arts Competition-dasu!
가오!
Here we go-dasu!
에잇, 네이놈! 건방진 짓을!
You bastard! How impudent of you!
동력실! 들리냐! 동력실!
Power room! Do you repeat? Power room!
여기가 동력실이다. 메가톤성이 어떻게 움직이는지 말하자면,
This is the power room. To explain about how Megaton Castle moves,
오괴승이라는 5명의 중이 염력으로 움직이고 있다.
5 monks named The Five Mystery Monks move it with psychokinesis.
동력실! 풀 파워!
Power room! Full power!
지지 않소!
We don't lose-dasu!
다들 파워 업이오!
Everyone, power up-dasu!
꽤 하는구나. 그러나 이건 못 피하겠지.
You're pretty good. But you won't evade this!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시! 괜찮냐, 무사시?!
Musashi! Are you okay, Musashi?!
괜찮소.
I'm fine-dasu.
자, 이게 부서지지 않는 동안 놈들을 바다에 빠트려 버리자!
Now, while this holds up, let's sink them into the sea!
이제 한계다!
It's at its limit!
탈출하자!
Let's escape!
하! 결국 얘들 장난감. 이 메가톤성의 적이 아니다!
Hah! I knew that was children's toy! It can't possibly be an enemy of this Megaton Castle!
자! 한번에 에도성을 깔아뭉개라!
Now, crush Edo Castle at once!
도쿠간류 님!
Lord Dokuganryu!
뭐야?!
What is it?!
동력실의 파워가 0이 되었습니다!
The power room isn't making any power!
뭣이?!
What?!
네이놈... 이 빚은 꼭 갚아 주겠다!
You bastards... This will be paid back!
비상용 로켓 불꽃 점화!
Emergency firecracker rocket, ignite!
흥이오! 우리 승리이오!
Hmph! We won-dasu!
-무사시!
-이야, 훌륭해, 훌륭해!
-Musashi!
-Good job! Good job!
해냈구나, 무사시.
You did it, Musashi.
아니, 모두의 덕분이오.
No, it's thanks to everyone-dasu.
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
오츠루, 무사했었소!
Otsuru, you're safe-dasu!
무사시 씨야말로 걱정했어, 나!
I was worried about you, Mr. Musashi!
싸워서 배고프지?
You must be hungry after that fighting!
자, 여기!
Have this!
우와, 감격이오! 전투 후의 단고는 제일 맛있소!
I'm so deeply happy-dasu! Dangos after a battle are the best-dasu!
센짱!
Sen-chan!
계속 바보짓만 하던 놈이 오늘은 대활약이구나! 그 뇌의 능력을 숨기고 있었구나!
You usual idiot did a great job today! You were hiding your brain capabilities!
아니아니, 그만하시오! 그만하시오!
No, no, stop it-dasu! Stop it-dasu!
자, 코지로 씨하고 여러분, 배고프시죠? 단고 드세요.
Now, Mr. Kojirō and everyone, you must be hungry! Have some dangos.
아, 예, 잘 먹겠습니다.
Oh, right, thank you!
네!
Yeah!
아, 내 단고!
My dangos!
-오츠루!
-야, 무사시, 웃어, 웃어!
-Otsuru!
-Hey, Musashi, smile! Smile!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
무서운 메가톤성은 무사시 일행의 우정 파워로 물리쳤다.
That fearful Megaton Castle was beaten off by the friendship power of Musashi and his friends.
그러나 무사시 앞에는 새로운 문제가.
But Musashi got a new problem.
그건 질투가 강한 오츠루였다.
That was Otsuru who is very jealous.
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
꽤나 남자친구를 찾지 못한 난폭한 말과 같은 센짱이, 무슨, 미남인 국왕 전하를 구하게 되고 말았소.
That unmanageable person Sen-chan's going to rescue the Highness who's really handsome,
after being unable to find a boyfriend for a long time-dasu!
거기에 다시 메가톤성이 공격해 와서 에도토피아에 큰 화재이오!
Megaton Castle came to attack again, and Edotopia's on big fire-dasu!
지라이얀 일행이 필사적으로 소화 작업을 하고 있지만 오츠루의 단고집이 불타버렸소!
Jiraiyan and others are doing their best to put off fire, but Otsuru's dango store is also burnt-dasu!
다음 이야기! 센히메의 사랑은 이기오
Next story! Senhime's Love Wins
질풍노도의 구운 단고오!
It's a stormy cooked dango-dasu!
다음 이야기
센히메의 사랑은
이기오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Senhime's Love
Wins
Look forwards for it!